<resources>
    <string name="app_name">My Application</string>

    <string name="Aman">
        Total Blocks = 8.

        <br> Boys Blocks = K01, K02.</br>
        <br> Girls Blocks = K03 , K04 , K05 , K06 , K07 , K08.</br>
        <br> Location : In Campus.</br>
           <br>   Desasiswa Aman Damai , Bangunan K10, </br>
         <br>     Universiti Sains Malaysia ,</br>
        <br>      11800 Gelugor ,Pulau Pinang.</br>
        <br>  Email Pej.: | Web: http://web.usm.my/amandamai |</br>
      <br>    No.Tel: 04-653 3203 |</br>
      <br>    No.Fax: 04-656 6571 </br>
    </string>

    <string name="Bakti">

        Total Blocks = 9

        <br> Undergrade Blocks = 2. </br>
        <br> Postgrade Blocks = 7. </br>
        <br> Location : In Campus.</br>
           <br>   Desasiswa Bakti Permai , </br>
         <br>     Universiti Sains Malaysia ,</br>
        <br>      11800 Gelugor ,Pulau Pinang.</br>
        <br>  Email : baktipermai@usm.my |</br>
      <br>    No.Tel: 04-653 3192 |</br>
      <br>    No.Fax: 04-656 4612</br>

    </string>

    <string name="Cahaya">

        Total Blocks = 3.

        <br> Student Blocks = 2 </br>
        <br> Management Office Blocks = 1 </br>
        <br> Location : In Campus </br>
           <br>   Desasiswa Cahaya Gemilang, Bangunan H33, </br>
         <br>     Universiti Sains Malaysia ,</br>
        <br>      11800 Gelugor ,Pulau Pinang.</br>
      <br>    No.Tel: 04-653 3339 </br>
      <br>    No.Fax: 04-656 5641</br>

    </string>

    <string name="Fajar">
        Total Blocks = 3.

        <br> Boys Blocks = F26 </br>
        <br> Girls Blocks = F25 </br>
        <br> Cafe = 1 block </br>
        <br> Location : In Campus </br>
           <br>   Desasiswa Aman Damai Fajar Harapan , </br>
         <br>     Universiti Sains Malaysia ,</br>
        <br>      11800 Gelugor ,Pulau Pinang.</br>
        <br>  Email:adfh@usm.my </br>
      <br>    No.Tel: 04-653 3619 </br>
      <br>    No.Fax: 04-656 6571 </br>
    </string>

    <string name="Indah">
        Total Blocks = 6

        <br> Boys Blocks = L12 </br>
        <br> Girls Blocks = L06, LO07, L11 </br>
        <br> Location : In Campus |</br>
           <br>   Desasiswa Indah Kembara,  </br>
         <br>     Universiti Sains Malaysia ,</br>
        <br>      11800 Gelugor ,Pulau Pinang.</br>
      <br>    No.Tel: 04-653 2489/2512 </br>
      <br>    No.Fax: 04-657 3223 </br>
    </string>

    <string name="Restu">
        Total Blocks = 2

        <br> Boys Blocks = M01 </br>
        <br> Girls Blocks = M02 </br>
        <br> Location : RST (Outside Campus) </br>
           <br>   Desasiswa Restu,  </br>
         <br>     Universiti Sains Malaysia ,</br>
        <br>      11800 Gelugor ,Pulau Pinang.</br>
        <br>  Email:restu@usm.my </br>
      <br>    No.Tel: 04-653 2739/4465 </br>
      <br>    No.Fax: 04-657 9966 </br>
    </string>

    <string name="Saujana">
        Total Blocks = 2

        <br> Girls Blocks = M03, M04 </br>
        <br> Location : RST (Outside Campus) </br>
           <br>  Pejabat Desasiswa Saujana, Blok M07, </br>
         <br>     Universiti Sains Malaysia ,</br>
        <br>      11800 Gelugor ,Pulau Pinang.</br>
      <br>    No.Tel: 04-653 4463 </br>
      <br>    No.Fax: 04-657 9924 </br>
    </string>

    <string name="Tekun">
        Total Blocks = 2

        <br> Boys Blocks = M05 </br>
        <br> Girls Blocks = M06 </br>
        <br> Location : RST (Outside Campus) </br>
           <br>   Desasiswa Tekun, </br>
         <br>     Universiti Sains Malaysia ,</br>
        <br>      11800 Gelugor ,Pulau Pinang.</br>
        <br>  Email: d_tekun@usm.my </br>
      <br>    No.Tel: 04-653 4451/4453</br>
      <br>    No.Fax: 04-657 4623 </br>
    </string>

    <string name="arts">
        <br> Dean email: dean_arts@usm.my </br>
        <br> D20 Building, opposite to CIMB Bank </br>
        <br> Telephone Number: 604 – 653 3888 ext 3621 / 3415 </br>
        <br> Facilities include Galeri Adiwarna which is an art exhibition </br>
        </string>

    <string name="biology">
    <br> Tel: (604)6533181 | Fax: (604) 6565125 </br>
    <br> Dean Email: dean_bio@usm.my </br>
    <br> G08 building, Persiaran Sains </br>
    <br> Five main research laboratories, namely, Plant Pathology Laboratory, Phytochemistry Laboratory, Biotechnology and Molecular Biology Laboratory, Microbiology Laboratory, and Fish Biology Laboratory. </br>
    <br> Houses teaching laboratories for Plant Pathology, Microbiology and Biotechnology. Academic staff offices are located within the two buildings. </br>
    <br> Supported by other facilities such as Electron Microscope Unit, Herbarium, Plant House and Fish House. </br>
    </string>

    <string name="chemical">
        <br> Telephone Number: +604 - 6533262     |  Fax:  +604 - 657485 </br>
        <br>  Dean email: r_adnan@usm.my (Professor Dr. Rohana Binti Adnan) </br>
       <br>  G09 Building </br>
       <br>  The school occupies a four storey building which houses research and teaching facilities. An annex was recently added due to the expansion of analytical and industrial chemistry programs. </br>
 </string>

    <string name="communication">
        <br> Tel : 04-653 3601/653 3602  |  Fax: 04-6577736 </br>
        <br> Email : dean_com@usm.my </br>
        <br> C10 Building </br>
        <br> Facilities: Film and Broadcast, Persuasive Communication, Journalism </br>
  </string>

    <string name="Computer">
       <br> Tel: +604-653 3647/4381| Fax: +604-653 3648 </br>
        <br> Email: cs@usm.my </br>
        <br> G31 Building </br>
        <br> Dean: Professor Dr. Bahari Belaton </br>
        <br> Facilities include a lecture hall, 4 computer laboratories, 2 tutorial rooms with projector, 1 student self-serve cafe with 3 vending machines, 1 student lounge, 2 elevators and 1 viva room. </br>
        <br> USM is ranked within the top 100 universities in the world for Computer Science and Information Systems (QS World University Rankings, 2017). </br>
</string>

    <string name="DistanceEdu">
       <br> Tel: +604-6536197 | Fax: +604-6576000 </br>
        <br> Email: tda_cde@usm.my </br>
        <br> Dean: Associate Professor Dr. Zoraini Wati M Abas </br>
        <br> E39 Building </br>
        <br> Oldest distance education program at university level in Malaysia </br>
    </string>

    <string name="EduScience">
        <br> Tel: 604-6533888 ext 3231 | Fax : 604-6572907 </br>
        <br> Email : dean_edu@usm.my </br>
        <br> Dean: Professor Dr. Hairul Nizam Ismail </br>
        <br> E43 Building  </br>
        <br> Facilities for School of Educational Sciences are as follows: </br>
        <br> Meeting Room, Digest Room, Coference Room, Special Education Room, Micro Education Rooms, Viva Room, Biology Lab, Computer Lab, Chemistry Lab, Mathematics Lab, Physics Lab,  Student Lounge, Poligraph Room, Counseling Room, Multi-Purpose Room, Research Rooms, Source Room, Sensory Room, SMART LAB, Auditorium. </br>
    </string>

    <string name="HBP">
        <br> Tel : +604-653 3888 | Fax : +604-658 9666  </br>
        <br> Email : hbp@usm.my   </br>
        <br> Dean: Assoc. Prof. Ir. Dr Abdul Naser Abdul Ghani </br>
        <br>  E49 Building </br>
        <br> The nation’s oldest built environment school. </br>
        <br> 7 undergraduate programs: architecture, interior design, building surveying, building technology, construction management, urban and regional planning, and quantity surveying.  </br>
    <br> Facilities provided are Structural Laboratory, Concrete and Cement Lab and Other Equipments </br>
</string>

    <string name="Humanities">
        <br> Phone: 604-6533888 | Fax: 604-6563707  </br>
        <br> Email: dean_hum@usm.my </br>
        <br> Dean: Professor Dr. Narimah Samat </br>
        <br> C11, C12 Building </br>
        <br> One of the oldest humanities faculties in Malaysia. </br>
        <br> Covers a wide spectrum of disciplines that include philosophy, religion, language, literature, translation, history, geography, and civilisation.   </br>
        <br> Facilities are Resource Room, Language Rooms, Audiovisual Lab,  Interpretation Lab, GIS Lab,  Archieve and Documentation Room, Hydrology Lab,  Computer Lab , Physical Geography Lab, Cartography Lab, Seminar/Viva Room, Meeting Rooms, Undergraduate Student Lounge, Postgraduate Karel Room  </br>
</string>

    <string name="IndusTech">
        <br> Tel: +604 653 2219 | Fax: +604-653 6375  </br>
        <br> Email: dean_ind@usm.my </br>
        <br> Dean: Professor Dr. Norli Ismail </br>
        <br> G07 Building </br>
        <br> The Food Tech laboratories: Food Processing Lab, Food Instrumental Analysis Lab, Food Chemical Analysis Lab </br>
        <br> The BPC Tech laboratories: Furniture Workshop, Pulp and Paper Testing Lab, Coatings Lab, Thermal Testing Lab </br>
        <br> The Env Tech laboratories: Energy Testing Unit,  Water moving in circular motion covariance flux and meteorological station that monitors environmental parameters. </br>
        <br> The Bioprocess Tech facilities: Cell Culture Lab, Fermentation Technology Lab, Microalgae Lab </br>
    </string>

    <string name="Language">
        <br> Tel: (60) 04-6533145/3158/3751/4141 | Fax: +604-6569122 </br>
        <br> Email: ppblt_courses@usm.my </br>
        <br> Dean: Prof. Dr. Salasiah Che Lah  </br>
        <br> D10 Building </br>
        <br> Has a Terminology Unit that is responsible for providing assistance to Dewan Bahasa dan Pustaka (DBP) in terminology building in Bahasa Malaysia. </br>
        <br> Services include translation, editing, interpreting, language consultancy and short-term and longterm language courses. </br>
        <br> Facilities are Resource Room, Language Laboratory and Computer Assisted Language </br>
</string>

    <string name="management">
        <br> Tel: +604-653 3984/3985/2520/3370 | Fax: +604-653 6375  </br>
        <br> E-mail: som@usm.my </br>
        <br> Dean: Professor Dr. Noor Hazlina Ahmad </br>
        <br> E45 Building </br>
        <br> Faculties available are Accounting, Business Analytics, Finance and Islamic Finance, International Business, Marketing, Operation Management, Stratergy and Organisational Management </br>
        <br> Facilities provided are Auditorium, Banquet Room, Conference Room, Computer Room, Foyer, Front Desk, PHD Room, Student Lounge, Meeting Room, SOM Building, Training Room, Viva Room </br>
    </string>

    <string name="Mathematics">
        <br> Tel : +604 653 3284 | Fax : +604 657 0910 </br>
        <br> E-Mail : dean_mat@usm.my </br>
        <br> Dean: Professor Dr. Hailiza Kamarulhaili </br>
        <br> G31 Building </br>
        <br> Programs available are Mathematics, Mathematics Modelling, Applied Statistics, Operations Research and Mathematics And Economy </br>
    </string>

    <string name="Pharmacy">
        <br> Tel : 604-6532211  |  Fax: 604-6570017 </br>
        <br> E-mail : dean_pha@usm.my </br>
        <br> Dean: Prof. Dr. Habibah Binti A Wahab </br>
        <br> J01 Building </br>
        <br> Services provided are Pharmacology, Physiology, Pharmaceutical Technology, Pharmaceutical Chemistry, Clinical Pharmacy, Social and Administrative Pharmacy </br>
    </string>

    <string name="Physics">
        <br> Tel : 604 653 3200 / 3198  |  Fax: 604 657 9150 </br>
        <br> Email :  dean_phy@usm.my </br>
        <br> Dean: Prof. Dr. Abdul Razak Ibrahim </br>
        <br> G06 Building </br>
        <br> Facilities are Energy Laboratory and Computer Lab </br>
        <br> Research areas: Condensed Matter Physics and X-ray Crystallography, Applied and Engineering Physics, Energy Studies, Geophysics, Astronomy and Atmospheric Science, Theoretical and Computational Physics and Medical Physics and Radiation Science </br>
    </string>

    <string name="Socialsciences">
        <br> Tel : +604-653 3369  | Fax : +604-657 0918  </br>
        <br> Email : dean_soc@usm.my  </br>
        <br> Dean: Professor Dr. Azlinda Binti Azman </br>
        <br> C06 Building(office) </br>
        <br> Facilities are Computer Lab, Conference Room, Graduate Hall and Meeting Room </br>
        <br> Focus on Anthropology and Sociology, Development Planning and Management, Economics, Political Science and Social Work </br>
    </string>

    <string name="about">

    <br> Finder Version 1.0.0 </br>
    <br> App developed and maintained by USM Students </br>
    <br> Optimised for Android versions after 6.0 only ( Marshmallow ) </br>
    <br> Help us to improve by clicking feedback button below  </br>

    </string>

</resources>